# Rakesh P R

Full Stack Developer

#### **Personal Info**

**Email** 

rakeshpr369@gmail.com

**Phone** 

+91-8078416369

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rakesh-p-r-612339161/

#### **Skills**

****
****
****
****
****

# Languages

English	****
Hindi	****
Malayalam	****
Tamil	****

# Hobby/Interest

Listening to music Travel Computer Tech Browsing Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Good knowledge of the best practices for web design, user experience, and speed.

## **Work History**

2022-03

#### **Full Stack Developer Intern**

- 2022-09

NULL CLASS, Remote

- Developing front end website architecture.
- Designing user interactions on web pages.
- Developing back-end website applications.
- · Creating servers and databases for functionality.

2021-08 - 2022-01

#### **Content Moderator**

Enhance Business Solutions Private Limited.

- Review and moderate the platform by following the policies, processes, and guidelines and providing decisions based on prescribed guidelines.
- · High-quality extraction of content delivered consistently
- · Focus on accuracy/eye for details
- Adapt and deliver high-quality extraction with accuracy, commitment, and consistency

2020-05

#### **IT Technical Support**

- 2021-06

Microtek International Pvt. Ltd.

- · Provide technical assistance with computer hardware and software
- Create and maintain tips and tricks solutions for online database and web site
- · Log bugs and enhancement requests
- Perform hardware and software installations, configurations and updates as needed

# **Education**

2022-12 Bachelor of (	Commerce
-----------------------	----------

BHARATHIAR UNIVERSITY

2014-03 XII, Computer Application

KPSMM VHSS VARODE

2012-03 High School, SSLC

SREE NARAYANA TRUST HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL

### **Certificates**

2022-03	Full Stack MERN Developer (Project StackOverflow Clone)
2020-09	Full Stack Web Developer
2020-11	Google IT Support
2020-10	The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing